Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Up with People Archives
1937-2015
(bulk 1970-1990)
MS 491
Up with People (Organization)
Papers, 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990). This collection contains papers related to the organization Up with People. The bulk of the material consists of photographic and audiovisual materials from Up with People performances and events as well as musical arrangements, programs and publications. Also included are some organizational records and memorabilia. A small amount of material is related to Moral Re-armament.
160 linear ft
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Further accruals are expected.
Historical Note
Up with People is an international educational nonprofit organization aimed at creating young adults with global understanding through musical performance, international tours and community service. Up with People emerged in 1965 from Sing Outs. Moral Re-armament, an international morality and spirituality movement, sponsored these shows which attracted young people with its positive message of love, honesty, purity and unselfishness. J. Blanton Belk, the founder of Up with People, incorporated in 1968 with the encouragement of President Dwight Eisenhower and German Chancellor Konrad Adenauer and then separated from Moral Re-armament. Headquartered in Denver, Colorado since 1993, Up with People began in Tucson, Arizona with the University of Arizona serving as the staging center for several months each year as new cast members- young men and women between 18 and 29 learned songs and choreography. Up with People has performed at a variety of notable events including the 1972 Olympic Games in Munich, four NFL Super Bowl half time shows and several World Expos as well as for dignitaries around the world. Up with People suspended its programs in 2000 but returned after reorganization in 2004. Today Up with People continues to use music as a way to create understanding between cultures and impact communities worldwide through service in order to create global citizens. It is an independent nonprofit, 501(c)(3) organization without any religious or political affiliations.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 10 series.
Series I: Organizational Records, 1937-2015
Subseries 1: Administrative Files, 1937-2015
Subseries 2: Promotional Material, 1960-1996
Subseries 3: Yearbooks, 1970-2000
Series II: Publications, 1938-1999
Subseries 1: Newspapers and Newsletters, 1966-1997
Subseries 2: Performance Programs, 1965-1999
Subseries 3: Song Books, 1938-1999
Subseries 4: Dare/Pace Magazine, 1964-1969
Series III: Scores, 1968-1994
Series IV: Sheet Music, 1937-2000
Series V: Music Translations, 1971-1995
Series VI: Symphony Arrangements, 1951-1998
Series VII: Photographic material, 1960-2010
Subseries 1: 35mm negatives, undated
Subseries 2: Marketing, 1965-2010
Subseries 3: People, 1960-1998
Subseries 4: Performances and Events, 1965-1999
Subseries 5: Photographic Albums, 1969-1999
Series VIII: Oversize Materials, 1965-1999
Subseries 1: Posters, 1965-1990
Subseries 2: Scores, 1970-1985
Subseries 3: Photographs and photographic albums, 1965-1982
Subseries 4: Scrapbooks, 1973-1999
Series IX: Audio Visual Materials, 1962-2009
Subseries 1: Record albums 1962-1990
Subseries 2: Audio 1965-2009
Subseries 3: Moving Images 1965-2000
Series X: Memorabilia 2009, undated
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of the papers of the organization Up with People. The bulk of the material includes photographic and audiovisual material from Up with People performances and events. It also contains musical arrangements including scores, sheet music, song translations and symphony arrangements, publications such as newsletters, programs and promotional material and organizational records including annual reports, yearbooks, correspondence and manuals.
Oxford Group; Moral Re-armament (Organization); Up With People (Organization); Colwell Brothers; Super Bowl; Olympic Games (20th: 1972: Munich, Germany); Sheet music; Correspondence; Newsletters; Songbooks; Photography Negatives; Photographs
Container List
- Series I: Organizational Records, 1937-2015
  The series contains reports, yearbooks, correspondence, and handbooks associated with Up with People. The series is divided into three subseries.
  - Subseries 1: Administrative Files, 1937-2015
    This subseries contains correspondence regarding Up with People events, tours, alumni and fans as well as manuals, staff informational packets, schedules and other employee handouts regarding different programs and the administration of the organization. Also included are materials related to Moral Re-armament. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - Allen’s Press Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Association Proposed Charter Bylaws, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Directory marketing, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alumni material, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alumni material, 1990-1992, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The American Way, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Arizona Highways, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Bank of Boston, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - The Best of Arizona, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bicentennial Program, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Blank letterhead, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - China (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - China (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Colorado Move, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence A-W, 1942-1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - COSFIET, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Education Program, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Educational Programs Information, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Event Coordinator Resource Manual (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Event Coordinator Resource Manual (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 50th Anniversary, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Financial Planner, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - The Forgotten War, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Frank Buchman’s Effect on the World Presentations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - General Motors 75th Anniversary, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Global Youth Leadership Curriculum, part 1, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Global Youth Leadership Curriculum, part 2, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Groundbreaking, 1992 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - IBM Viewpoint, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Interoffice News, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Invest Yourself, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Island House, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Jack Parr Television Special, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Macy’s, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Merv Griffin Show, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mexico tour, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Money Magazine public service ad, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Moral Re-Armament, 1937-1949 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Moral Re-Armament, 1950-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Moral Re-Armament- Eleanor B. Allen, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Moral Re-Armament- Drugstore Revolution, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Moral Re-Armament- Plays, 1947-1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Moral Re-Armament- Your Part in Winning the War, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - National Awareness Plan, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - National Student Life Initiative Manual, Part 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - National Student Life Initiative Manual, Part 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - National Student Life Initiative, The Day of Peace Program, Peace RAP, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Pearl S. Buck Foundation, Inc., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Photojournalism Cast A reports, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Pope John Paul reception, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Proclamation examples, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Project Pride, Cast Member Workshop Handbook, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Project Pride Handbook, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Project Pride, part 1, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Project Pride, part 2, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Promotion in Europe manual, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Promotion Manual, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Promotion Manual, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Promotion Manual, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Promotion Manual, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Reader’s Digest, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Rhythm of the World, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Rhythm of the World Promotional Manual, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Center Assembly, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco Television, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Scheduling Department Seminar, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Seventeen Magazine, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Show Script, Mr. Don Birdsail, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Social Impacts and Lasting Benefits, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Southwest Gas, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Soviet tour (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Soviet tour (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Sponsor Promotion Manual, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Staff Operation Schedule, cast schedule, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Staging and Department Records, Production and Choreographic, part 1, 1978-1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Staging and Department Records, Production and Choreographic, part 2, 1978-1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Staging Journal, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Student Handbook, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Successful Meeting, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Summer staging (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Summer staging (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Super Bowl XVI, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl XX (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl XX (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl XX lighting, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl XX program ad, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Teen Generation magazine, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Time for the Music, part 1, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Time for the Music, part 2, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Time for the Music, part 3, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Tour highlights (1 of 2), 1975-1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Tour highlights (2 of 2), 1975-1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Tour schedules (1 of 2), 1969-1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Tour schedules (2 of 2), 1969-1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Tour schedules (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Tour schedules (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Tour schedules (1 of 2), 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Tour schedules (2 of 2), 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Tucson Media, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 25th Anniversary Celebration, part 1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 25th Anniversary Celebration, part 2, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 25th Anniversary Celebration, part 3, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 25th Anniversary Celebration, part 4, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 25th Anniversary Celebration, part 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - University of Arizona Homecoming, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Up with People in Chicago, part 1, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Up with People in Chicago, part 2, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Various Memorandums and Schedules, 1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Western Canadian tour, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Winter staging (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Winter staging (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Winter staging, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - World in Motion Merchandise Campaign, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - World in Motion Program, Video and Audio Cassette material, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - World in Motion, Un Mundo en Accion, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - World Smart Manual, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - World Smart Meeting Notes, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - World Smart Student Leadership Curriculum, part 1, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - World Smart Student Leadership Curriculum, part 2, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - World Smart Student Leadership Curriculum, part 3, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2: Promotional Materials, 1960-1996
    This series contains brochures, flyers, pamphlets and press releases related to Up with People programs and performances as well as clippings related to the Up with People organization. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - Alumni Pamphlets, 1984-1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Brochures and Flyers, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Brochures and Flyers (1 of 6), 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Brochures and Flyers (2 of 6), 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Brochures and Flyers (3 of 6), 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Brochures and Flyers (4 of 6), 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Brochures and Flyers (5 of 6), 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Brochures and Flyers (6 of 6), 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Brochures and Flyers, 1980-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Brochures and Flyers, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Brochures and Flyers- Drafts, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Brochures and Flyers- Translated, 1970-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Carroll College, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Clippings and articles, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Clippings and articles, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Clippings and articles, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Clippings and articles, 1985-1996, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Clippings- China, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Clippings- Europe, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Clippings- Move to Colorado, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Clippings- Super Bowl, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fact sheets, 1970-1977, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper mats, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Press kits, 1969-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Press kits, 1990-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Press kits- CBS, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Press kits folders, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Press quotes, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Press releases, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Press releases, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Press releases, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Press releases, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Press releases, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Press releases- Board, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Press releases- Finland, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Press releases- Smithfields, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Press releases- Spanish, 1975, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Press releases- Staff, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Press releases-Sweden, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Press routing copies (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press routing copies (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Radio spots, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Recipe Collection, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Tickets and Drafts, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - World Sing out Festival, Up with People (1 of 2), 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - World Sing out Festival, Up with People (2 of 2), 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Yearbooks, 1970-2000
    This subseries contains yearbooks produced by Up with People as well as other writings related to the experiences of different cast members. It is arranged chronologically.
    - 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 1970, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 1989-2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Series II: Publications, 1938-1999
  This series contains publications distributed by Up with People including newsletters, programs, songbooks and magazines. It is divided into four subseries.
  - Subseries 1: Newspapers and Newsletters, 1966-1997
    This series contains news publications produced by and for Up with People and alumni. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - Alumni News, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Sing Out Cincinnati, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Tomorrow’s American, 1966 July-December (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Tomorrow’s American, 1967 January-July (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Tomorrow’s American, 1967 August- December (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Tomorrow’s American News, 1968 January- May (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Tomorrow’s American News, 1968 June-December (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Tomorrow’s American News, 1969 January-July (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Tomorrow’s American News, 1969 September-December (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Tomorrow’s American NewsDay, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Up with People Associates Report, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Up with People Connections, 1990; 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Up with People Dialogue, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Up with People News, March 1971-June 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Up with People News, 1974 April-December (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Up with People News, 1975 February-December (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Up with People News, 1976 February-May (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Up with People News, Summer 1976-Winter 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Up with People, Spring 1977-Fall 1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Up with People News, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Up with People News, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Up with People Newsletter, 1983-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Up with People Perspective, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Up with People Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Up with People Sponsor Connection, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Various Alumni Newsletters, 1988-1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 2: Performance Programs, 1965-1999
    This series contains programs from Up with People performances.
    - 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 1970-1979 (1 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 1970-1979 (2 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 1970-1979 (3 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 1970-1979 (4 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - 1970-1979 (5 of 5) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1980-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1980-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1990-1999 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1990-1999 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Sing Out, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3: Songbooks, 1938-1999
    This series contains books of songs related to Up with People.
    - Colwell Song Album, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - I Like to Sing, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - MRA choral songs, 1948-1959 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Publishing song books (1 of 4), 1938-1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Publishing song books (2 of 4), 1938-1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Publishing song books (3 of 4), 1938-1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Publishing song books (4 of 4), 1938-1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Show lyrics, 1985-1999 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Sing Out, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Songs from Caux Volume I-III, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Songs from Caux Volume IV-V, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - The Up with People Song Book Vol.1-5, 1969-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - The Up with People Song Book Vol. 6-10, 1977-1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - The Up with People Song Book Vol. 11-13, 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - The Up with People Song Book Vol. 14-15, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Vocal book, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Vocal book, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 4: Dare/Pace Magazine, 1964-1969
    This series contains a run of Dare/Pace magazine. Pace Magazine (previously known as Dare Magazine) was a monthly magazine produced by Pace Publications. Pace Publications was a division of Moral Re-armament and also produced some Up with People record albums. It is arranged chronologically.
    - October/November 1964-October 1966, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - November 1966-July 1967, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - August 1967-April 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - May 1968-December 1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - January 1968-July 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - September 1969-August 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Series III: Scores, 1968-1994
  The series contains scores used by Up with People. Scores contain the music for the entire orchestra. It is arranged alphabetically according to score title with several scores contained in each folder.
  - ABBA Dancing Queen- Ah! Simon Moine Voulair Danser, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Alberta Bound- Arizona Highways Instrumental, 1976-1993 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Ashes, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Australian Melody – Ayiko, 1980-1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Back in Style – Back in Style IV, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Battle Hymn of the Republic – Black & White, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bopping – Bitte Mand I Knibe, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Breaking New Ground – Bye Bye Mon Cowboy, 1975-1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Caballito Nicoyano – Cadillac Medley, 1984, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Canadian Medley, 1976, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Canadian Railroad Trilogy – Chante La Ta Chanson, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Chaser – Christmas Medley, 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ci Sara – Clavelitos, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Coca Cola ’85- Coming of Age, 1979-1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Consider Yourself – Country Medley, 1978-1979, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Dawning – Do Wop Medley, 1978-1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Drupa – Dutch Song ’84, 1984, 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Earth Ship – Eine Kleine Night Muzak, 1979, 1984, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - El Adios – El Rascapetate, 1977-1981, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - En Sjohndrades Jubileumstrail – Es Burebuebli, 1973-1991 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - European Medley – Everything I do I do it for you, 1977, 1993, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Faces – Flashdance/Rock and Roll is King, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Flickorana I Smaland, 1972, 1984, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Freedom Isn’t Free – The Future Starts Today, 1984, 1989, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Galway Shawl – Give the Jukebox a Kick, 1976-1991, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Go For it All – Good –Time Oldies Medley, 1994, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Gopak – Gymnastik, 1979-1987, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Haleakala – Hey you out there, 1977-1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - H.F.C. – A Hundred Years, 1977-1990, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - I Don’t Want to Rule the World – I’d rather be a Cowboy, 1977, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - If I had a $1,000,000 – Int’l Med for Album, 1979, 1988, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - International Med for LP – I’s the B’Y, 1970-1981, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Italian Medley, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Italian Medley '85 Tour – It’s Not Easy, 1985, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - J’Aime La Vie – Just People Brick by Brick, 1978-1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Keepin’ in Touch –Kostervalsen, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - La Bamba – Let’s Go Dancing Medley, 1977-1978, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Libre – LLamarada, 1975-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Load – Lost am I, 1979, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Maailma on Matkakaleua – Mamy Tylko Siebie, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Man’s Gotta Go Somewhere – A Memorable Tune, 1969, 1980, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Merry Christmas to You All – Mexican Medley, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Mexican Medley, 1977-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mexican Medley – Modern Medley, 1975-1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Mozart Rocks – My Songs, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mon Pays – Mule Skinner Blues, 1968-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Nardos – New Dimension, 1984, 1992, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New York, New York – Nova Scotia Song, 1979, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Oak Tree – On a California Morning, 1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - On the Banks of My Own Lovely Lee – Oxdans, 1982, 1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Panasonic Song –Merry Christmas Peru, 1980-1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pescao – Play Off #1, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)